

This font is based on some destination sings of some Spanish trains (440, 447…).

If you want to add a realistic effect, use three layers, the bottom layer should contain a dark brown dots pattern, you can create it with the "dark shade" character ▓ (U+2593). The medium layer must contain the text with a bright colour. The top layer is a clone of the medium layer, but it should be blurred. Maybe you can need a fourth blurred layer (a bit more than third) with a light colour in the third layer.

You can create a solid background pattern without vertical spaces using the "black vertical rectangle" ▮ (U+25AE)
which fill 8 rows instead of 7.

Feel free to use it and modify it.


You can create the backgrounds copying these symbols:
▓
▮

The second symbol creates a background without spaces.
In some editors You could need to modify the linespacing.